<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<strings>

  <game_saved>
    <en-gb>Game Saved</en-gb>
  </game_saved>

  <test_level_name>
    <en-gb>Test Level</en-gb>
  </test_level_name>

  <health_upgrade_notification>
    <en-gb>Max Health Increased</en-gb>
  </health_upgrade_notification>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll>
    <en-gb>The ROLL technique. Rolling can be used to evade enemy projectiles. You can also roll just before landing from a fall to avoid slowing down. Press the LEFT BUMPER (LB on Xbox pad, L1 on PlayStation pad) to roll.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll_steamdeck>
    <en-gb>The ROLL technique. Rolling can be used to evade enemy projectiles. You can also roll just before landing from a fall to avoid slowing down. Press L1 to roll.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll_steamdeck>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash>
    <en-gb>The downward SMASH technique. Smash through obstacles with this technique. Press the RIGHT BUMPER (RB on Xbox pad, R1 on PlayStation pad) in mid-air to trigger.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash_steamdeck>
    <en-gb>The downward SMASH technique. Smash through obstacles with this technique. Press R1 in mid-air to trigger.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash_steamdeck>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion>
    <en-gb>The FOCUS technique. Slow down time. Hold the LEFT TRIGGER (LT on Xbox pad, L2 on PlayStation pad) to activate.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion_steamdeck>
    <en-gb>The FOCUS technique. Slow down time. Hold L2 to activate.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion_steamdeck>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kDeflection>
    <en-gb>The DEFLECT technique. Deflect projectiles with your knives and your sword. Incredibly effective when attacked by large groups of enemies.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kDeflection>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kBombUnlock>
    <en-gb>A gifted warrior such as yourself has earned the right to wield this potent weapon. At a price. Press IN the LEFT THUMBSTICK (L3) to use.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kBombUnlock>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kSpeedIncrease>
    <en-gb>The AGILITY technique. Move at a quicker pace.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kSpeedIncrease>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kProjectileDamageIncrease>
    <en-gb>The EXTRA DAMAGE technique. A huge increase to your attack damage.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kProjectileDamageIncrease>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kProjectileSpeedIncrease>
    <en-gb>The EXTRA THROWING SPEED technique. Throw projectiles at a much faster rate.</en-gb>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kProjectileSpeedIncrease>

  <paper_pickup_title_test>
    <en-gb>BY ORDER OF THE SHOGUNATE</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_title_test>
  
  <paper_pickup_desc_test>
    <en-gb>Eliminate all threats and secure the forts. Leave no ... [illegible] ... and return all ...[illegible]</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_desc_test>

  <key_name_granary>
    <en-gb>Haruki's Key</en-gb>
  </key_name_granary>

  <key_desc_granary>
    <en-gb>A key with a note: "Haruki - The Forest Granary"</en-gb>
  </key_desc_granary>

  <key_name_dojo>
    <en-gb>The Dojo Key</en-gb>
  </key_name_dojo>

  <key_desc_dojo>
    <en-gb>It looks like this key opens up the Dojo.</en-gb>
  </key_desc_dojo>

  <suicide_note_name>
    <en-gb>Haruhiko's note</en-gb>
  </suicide_note_name>

  <suicide_note_desc>
    <en-gb>I've had enough. You'll find most of her body in the water by the falls.</en-gb>
  </suicide_note_desc>

  <dojo_closed_name>
    <en-gb>DOJO NOTE</en-gb>
  </dojo_closed_name>

  <dojo_closed_desc>
    <en-gb>The dojo is closed until further notice. Military riders are enroute and if you are reading this you need to evacuate as soon as possible.</en-gb>
  </dojo_closed_desc>

  <paper_pickup_title_granary_key_hint>
    <en-gb>Grain Supply Status</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_title_granary_key_hint>

  <paper_pickup_desc_granary_key_hint>
    <en-gb>Grain levels critical. 
           Requesting an increase in supply. 
           Granary key misplaced by Haruki. 
           Haruki's location unknown.</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_desc_granary_key_hint>

  <save_shrine_hint_title>
    <en-gb>Kato's note</en-gb>
  </save_shrine_hint_title>

  <save_shrine_hint_desc>
    <en-gb>I found a nearby hotspring. The healing waters saved me from my own memories. I feel like a new man. Can I make up for my sins?</en-gb>
  </save_shrine_hint_desc>

  <paper_pickup_gametip>
    <en-gb>GAME TIP</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_gametip>

  <paper_pickup_gametip_projectile>
    <en-gb>Hold the RIGHT THUMBSTICK to throw a flying dagger in any direction. You can move independently with the LEFT THUMBSTICK. Press the RIGHT TRIGGER (RT on Xbox pad, R2 on PlayStation pad) to Jump.</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_gametip_projectile>

  <paper_pickup_gametip_projectile_steamdeck>
    <en-gb>Hold the RIGHT THUMBSTICK to throw a flying dagger in any direction. You can move independently with the LEFT THUMBSTICK. Press R2 to Jump.</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_gametip_projectile_steamdeck>

  <paper_pickup_gametip_death>
    <en-gb>When you die you will lose all of your current orbs but will keep all techniques acquired, keys and other pickups.</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_gametip_death>

  <key_name_tools>
    <en-gb>Tools</en-gb>
  </key_name_tools>

  <key_desc_tools>
    <en-gb>An assortment of woodworking tools. These could be useful for repairing something broken.</en-gb>
  </key_desc_tools>

  <key_name_village_hut>
    <en-gb>Hut Key</en-gb>
  </key_name_village_hut>

  <key_desc_village_hut>
    <en-gb>This key looks like it would open one of the common huts.</en-gb>
  </key_desc_village_hut>
  
<paper_pickup_cave_clue_name>
    <en-gb>Himari's Note</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_cave_clue_name>
  
<paper_pickup_cave_clue_desc>
    <en-gb>I told Akio about the hidden cave earlier. He was mad at me. He said it was too dangerous diving beneath the waterfall. I told him I had seen a stream of bubbles and had to investigate. That's what an adventurer does.</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_cave_clue_desc>

  <broken_boat_message_title>
    <en-gb>Damaged Boat</en-gb>
  </broken_boat_message_title>

  <broken_boat_message_desc>
    <en-gb>A wooden boat that seems to have smashed up on the rocks. It needs repairing.</en-gb>
  </broken_boat_message_desc>

  <paper_pickup_strange_stones_title>
    <en-gb>Himari's Note</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_strange_stones_title>
  
  <paper_pickup_strange_stones_desc>
    <en-gb>The enemy is doing everything in their power to bring suffering and misery to our home. They blocked our food and water storage with these large stones. They look weak at the top, I wonder is there something we can use to SMASH them?</en-gb>
  </paper_pickup_strange_stones_desc>
</strings>
