<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<strings>

  <game_saved>
    <en-gb>Game Saved</en-gb>
    <pt-br>Jogo Salvo</pt-br>
    <de>Max. Gesundheit erhöht</de>
  </game_saved>

  <test_level_name>
    <en-gb>Test Level</en-gb>
    <pt-br>Test Level</pt-br>
    <de>Test Level</de>
  </test_level_name>

  <health_upgrade_notification>
    <en-gb>Max Health Increased</en-gb>
    <pt-br>Max Health Increased</pt-br>
    <de>Max Health Increased</de>
  </health_upgrade_notification>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll>
    <en-gb>The ROLL technique. Time your rolls on big landings to avoid a delay.</en-gb>
    <pt-br>A técnica ROLL Tempo seus rolos em grandes aterrissagens para evitar um atraso.</pt-br>
    <de>Die ROLL-Technik. Zeit für große Landungen, um eine Verzögerung zu vermeiden.</de>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kRoll>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash>
    <en-gb>The downward SMASH technique. Smash through obstacles with this technique. </en-gb>
    <pt-br>A técnica descendente de SMASH. Esmagar os obstáculos com esta técnica.</pt-br>
    <de>Die abwärts gerichtete SMASH-Technik. Besiege Hindernisse mit dieser Technik.</de>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kDownwardDash>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion>
    <en-gb>The FOCUS technique. Slow down time. TODO</en-gb>
    <pt-br>A técnica FOCUS. Diminua o tempo. FAÇAM</pt-br>
    <de>Die FOCUS-Technik. Zeit verlangsamen. MACHEN</de>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kSlowMotion>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kCrouchJump>
    <en-gb>The CROUCH-JUMP technique. Crouch down and then jump to reach higher highs.</en-gb>
    <pt-br>A técnica CROUCH-JUMP. Agache-se e pule para alcançar máximas mais altas.</pt-br>
    <de>Die CROUCH-JUMP-Technik. Crouch down und springe dann zu höheren Höhen.</de>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kCrouchJump>

  <dojo_scroll_desc_kDeflection>
    <en-gb>The DEFLECT technique. Deflect projectiles with your knives and your sword.</en-gb>
    <pt-br>A técnica DEFLECT. Desvie projéteis com suas facas e sua espada.</pt-br>
    <de>Die DEFLECT-Technik. Lenken Sie Projektile mit Ihren Messern und Ihrem Schwert ab.</de>
  </dojo_scroll_desc_kDeflection>

  <paper_pickup_title_test>
    <en-gb>BY ORDER OF THE SHOGUNATE</en-gb>
    <pt-br>PELA ORDEM DE SHOGUNATE</pt-br>
    <de>Die DEFLECT-Technik. Lenken Sie Projektile mit Ihren Messern und Ihrem Schwert ab.</de>
  </paper_pickup_title_test>
  
  <paper_pickup_desc_test>
    <en-gb>Eliminate all threats and secure the forts. Leave no ... [illegible] ... and return all ...[illegible]</en-gb>
    <pt-br>Elimine todas ameaças e proteja os fortes. Não deixe ... [Ilegível] ... e retorne todos ... [Ilegível] ...</pt-br>
    <de>Die DEFLECT-Technik. Lenken Sie Projektile mit Ihren Messern und Ihrem Schwert ab.</de>
  </paper_pickup_desc_test>
</strings>
